Guide to the Glenway Wescott Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Writings, 1921-84; Series III; 30.87; (74 boxes)
  - LECTURES, BROADCASTS AND SPEECHES
    - Academic presentations
      - [Unidentified locations]
        - [Various subjects], notecards, n.d. (Box 322, Folder 3157)
    - Art subjects
      - [re: Artists], notecards, n.d. (Box 323, Folder 3158-3162)
        [Possibly written with or presented
        by Monroe Wheeler]
      - "Factualism of American Painting", notecards, n.d.
      - "Historic exhibitions", notecards, n.d. (Box 323, Folder 3163)
      - "The Literary and the Pictorial"
        - Notebook, ca. 1955-56 (Box 323, Folder 3164)
        - Notes, 1954-56 (Box 323, Folder 3165)
        - Research correspondence, 1955-56 (Box 323, Folder 3166)
        - Invitation to lecture at the Frick Collection [as "The Pictorial and the Literary"], 1956 Jan 14 (Box 323, Folder 3167)
    - "Invitation to Learning"
      - Emily Brönte's Wuthering Heights, notes and notecards, 1944 Apr 18 (Box 324, Folder 3168)
      - Charles Dougherty's Arabia Deserta, notecards and transcript, 1944 Oct 29 (Box 324, Folder 3169)
      - Norman Douglas's South Wind, notes, 1945 Jul 22 (Box 324, Folder 3170)
      - Theodore Dreiser's The Titan, notes and notecards, 1947 Aug 24 (Box 324, Folder 3171)
      - T. E. Lawrence's Seven Pillars of Wisdom, notes and notecards, 1945 Jun 10 (Box 324, Folder 3172)
      - W. Somerset Maugham's The Moon and Sixpence, transcripts, 1947 Aug 31 (Box 324, Folder 3173)
      - Walter Pater's Marius the Epicurian, notes, n.d. (Box 324, Folder 3174)
      - Charles Reade's The Cloister and the Hearth, notecards and transcript, [1945?] Apr 14 (Box 324, Folder 3175)
      - George Santayana's The Sense of Beauty, transcript, 1949 Apr 10 (Box 324, Folder 3176)
      - George Bernard Shaw's Saint Joan, notecards and transcript, with notes, 1947 Sep 7 (Box 324, Folder 3177)
      - Leo Tolstoy's Anna Karenina, notecards, 1948 Apr 22 (Box 324, Folder 3178)
    - "The Open Mind" [NBC television]
      - "The American Novel Today", transcript, 1962 Nov (Box 324, Folder 3179)
      - "An Open Mind Profile: Katherine Anne Porter Talks with Glenway Wescott and Eric F. Goldman", transcripts with cover letter, 1962 May (Box 324, Folder 3180)
    - Social presentations
      - Book and Author Luncheon, Hotel Astor, [re: Apartment in Athens ], notecards and draft, typescript and mimeograph, 1945 Apr 10 (Box 324, Folder 3181)
      - "Dinner in honor of Joseph Campbell", program, 1983 Dec 4
      - The Dutch Treat Club, [re: Apartment in Athens ], notecards, 1945 May 1 (Box 324, Folder 3182)
      - The Eclectic Club, [re: The Pilgrim Hawk ], draft, typescript, corrected, 1941 Feb 26 (Box 324, Folder 3183)
      - The Eclectic Club, [re: wartime writing], draft, typescript, corrected, 1941 Dec 17 (Box 324, Folder 3184)
      - "For Mrs. Charles", [re: The Pilgrim Hawk, drafts, typescript, corrected, 1941 Feb 26 (Box 325, Folder 3185)
      - "For Mrs. W. Murray Crane", "The Way to Go Home", draft, typescript carbon, 1942 Mar 31 (Box 325, Folder 3186)
      - PEN Club, [re: Propaganda novels], notecards, 1952 Oct 9 (Box 325, Folder 3187)
      - Philadelphia Art Alliance, "Why I Write Fiction" panel discussion, announcement, 1959 Jan (Box 325, Folder 3188)
      - The Poetry Center, [re: Forster's Maurice ], announcement, 1971 (Box 325, Folder 3189)
      - [Speech at girls' softball team party, notecards], 1960 Nov
      - Westport Women's Club, [re: The Pilgrim Hawk ], draft, typescript, corrected, 1941 Nov 3 (Box 325, Folder 3190)
      - The Woman Pays Club, [re: definition of the novel], draft, typescript, 1941 Jan 7 (Box 325, Folder 3191)
      - [Unidentified locations]
        - [re: Apartment in Athens ], draft, typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 325, Folder 3192)
        - [re: Images of Truth ], notebook pages, ca. 1962 (Box 325, Folder 3193)
    - Success magazine [WOR radio]
      - Broadcast transcripts, 1945 Apr 5 (Box 325, Folder 3194)
    - War Bond Rallies
      - "Chicago Mar 10 1945", notecards, 1945 Mar 10 (Box 325, Folder 3195)
      - "Extra Ending", notecards (Box 325, Folder 3196)
      - "For the High Schools", notecards, ca. 1944 Dec (Box 325, Folder 3197)
      - "Notes for extra speech", notes, n.d. (Box 325, Folder 3198)
      - "Philadelphia April 9 and New York April 10 1945", notecards, 1945 Apr (Box 325, Folder 3199)
      - "Special intro and conclusion for the air-cadets at Waco", notecards (Box 325, Folder 3200)
      - "Ten Minutes for Texas", notecards, ca. 1944 Dec (Box 325, Folder 3201)
      - "Two Minutes", notecards, n.d. (Box 325, Folder 3202)
    - [Untitled program]
      - [Discussion with Katherine Anne Porter, GW, Tom Sullivan, Frances Stieloff and Walter Kiernan], transcript, [ca. 1962] (Box 325, Folder 3203)
  - WRITINGS ABOUT GLENWAY WESCOTT
    - Cowley, Malcolm, "The Last of the Lost Generation", printed version, Esquire, 1963 Jul
    - [Entry in Contemporary Literary Criticism ], printed version, photocopy, n.d. (Box 326, Folder 3204)
    - Ferlazzo, Paul J., "The Midwest and the Expatriate in the Fiction of Glenway Wescott", typescript, photocopy, 1977 (Box 326, Folder 3205)
    - Gado, Frank, "Glenway Wescott on Writers and Writing" [interview], printed version, Symposium, 1966 (Box 326, Folder 3206)
    - Kahn, Sy, "The Artist at Work", printed version, Papers on English Language and Literature, 1965 (Box 326, Folder 3207)
    - Kohler, Dayton, "Glenway Wescott: Legend Maker", printed version, The Bookman, 1931 Apr (Box 326, Folder 3208)
    - Kida, Takeyoshi, "The Peregrination of Glenway Wescott", printed version, Jimbungaku, 1962 Jul (Box 326, Folder 3209)
    - Overton, Grant, The Harper's Prize Novel Competition, printed version, 1932 (Box 326, Folder 3210)
    - Quinn, Patrick F., "The Case History of Glenway Wescott", printed version, Frontier and Midland, 1938 (Box 326, Folder 3211)
    - Stegner, Wallace, "Re-discovery: Wescott's Goodbye Wisconsin ", printed version, The Southern Review, 1970 (Box 326, Folder 3212)
    - Uccle, Girard d', [Feature on GW for "Ici New York" radio show], transcript, corrected, 1949 Feb 3 (Box 326, Folder 3213)
      Includes letter from Girard d'Uccle
  - WRITINGS OF OTHERS
    - Bartlett, Peter
      - "Married Bliss and Dirty Linen" [play about Maugham], typescript, photocopy, 1982 (Box 327, Folder 3214)
    - Butts, Mary
      - [Collection of poems], typescript, n.d. (Box 327, Folder 3215)
        Includes: "Chateau Gaillard",
        "Pythian Ode",
        "On Véxin",
        "Avenue Montaigne",
        and "Thinking of Saints and of
        Petronius Arbiter"
    - Cavafy, Constantin
      - "Their Beginning", [copy] typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 327, Folder 3216)
    - Chandlee, Will
      - "The Collectors", typescript carbon, 1957 Apr (Box 327, Folder 3217)
      - [Collection of short sketches], typescript and carbon (Box 327, Folder 3218)
    - Clark, Kenneth
      - Address on "Art and Society", typescript, mimeograph, 1959 Nov 2 (Box 327, Folder 3219)
    - Cocteau, Jean and Raymond Radiguet
      - "Paul et Virginie", typescript, n.d. (Box 327, Folder 3220)
    - Dryansky, G. Y.
      - "Something of Great Quality" [biography of Pauline de Rothschild], typescript, photocopy, n.d. (Box 327, Folder 3221)
    - Eiseley, Loren
      - "Singers of Life" [excerpt from The Judgement of Birds ], typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 327, Folder 3222)
    - Flanner, Hildegarde
      - If There is Time, printed version, photocopy, 1942 (Box 327, Folder 3223)
    - Ford, Hugh
      Four Lives in Paris
      - Prospectus, typescript, photocopy, n.d.
      - [Section on George Antheil], draft, typescript, photocopy, n.d. (Box 327, Folder 3225)
      - Jacket copy, draft, typescript, photocopy, n.d. (Box 327, Folder 3226)
    - Gathorne-Hardy, Robert
      - "The Thorn in the Desert", typescript carbon, 1938-39 (Box 327, Folder 3227)
    - Goudeket, Maurice
      - "The Delights of Growing Old", excerpts, holograph, n.d. (Box 327, Folder 3228)
    - Hagen, Beulah
      - "Stairway to Literary Fame", printed version, ALA Bulletin, 1956 Mar (Box 327, Folder 3229)
    - Justema, William
      - "Between Us" [collection of poems], typescript, 1938 (Box 327, Folder 3230)
    - Kirstein, Lincoln
      - "Magic Carpet" [play], typescript, photocopy, 1967 (Box 328, Folder 3231)
      - "Memorial" [poem], typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 328, Folder 3232)
    - Lebeck, Michael
      - English translation of Heinrich von Kleist's "About Marionettes", printed version, photocopy, 1971 (Box 328, Folder 3233)
      - "At First Sight", typescript, photocopy, n.d. (Box 328, Folder 3234)
      - "Work A Way", typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 328, Folder 3235)
    - Lewis, Janet
      - "Mulberry Street", printed version, photocopy, 1981 (Box 328, Folder 3236)
    - Lynes, George Platt
      - "Photographs", draft, typescript carbon and printed version, Dance Index, 1944 (Box 328, Folder 3237)
    - Lynes, Russell
      - "Incident at Villa Viciosa", galley proof, 1967 (Box 328, Folder 3238)
    - Maugham, W. Somerset
      - "Of Human Bondage: with a Digression on the Art of Fiction", printed version, annotated, photocopy, 1946 (Box 328, Folder 3239)
        Includes: letter [copy] from Marianne
        Moore to GW
    - Mohair, John P.
      - "The Psychiatric Approach to the Juvenile Offender at the New Jersey State Home for Boys", typescript, mimeograph, 1954 Oct 20 (Box 328, Folder 3240)
    - Moore, Marianne
      - "To Yvor Winters", printed version, Sequoia, photocopy, 1961 (Box 328, Folder 3241)
    - Mortimer, Raymond
      - "St. Monroe", holograph, n.d. (Box 328, Folder 3242)
    - Pagano, Mark
      - [Collection of essays and poems], typescript, corrected, 1982 (Box 328, Folder 3243)
    - Phelps, Robert
      - [Review of The Other Victorians by Steven Marcus], printed version, Book Find News (Box 328, Folder 3244)
    - Pomeroy, Ralph
      - "Birthday and Other Poems", typescript carbon, 1957 Oct 3 (Box 328, Folder 3245)
      - [Collection of poems], typescript and carbon, ca. 1948-58 (Box 328, Folder 3246)
    - Porter, Katherine Anne
      - "Morning Song of the Tinker's Bitch" and "Anniversary in a Country Cemetery", typescript carbon [copies] (Box 328, Folder 3247)
    - Prockup, Joannah
      - "Francis" and "Poems", typescript and holograph, carbon, photocopy (Box 328, Folder 3248)
    - Reventlow, Lucie Marie
      - [Collection of memoir essays], holograph and typescript, corrected (Box 328, Folder 3249)
      - "An Odyssey Without Love Affairs", typescript carbon, ca. 1967 (Box 328, Folder 3250)
        Includes: Letter from LMR to Pauline
        de Rothschild
    - Roberts, Elizabeth Maddox
      - "Horse", typescript, n.d. (Box 328, Folder 3251)
        Includes: letter from MW to Richard
        Wheeler
    - Rosco, Jerry
      - "Italian Boys", printed version, Blueboy, 1980 Nov (Box 328, Folder 3252)
      - "Three Friends", typescript, photocopy, 1978 (Box 328, Folder 3253)
    - Rothschild, Pauline de
      - "At Kizhi", printed version, Vogue, 1969 Dec (Box 328, Folder 3254)
      - [Collection of short essays], typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 328, Folder 3255)
      - "The Irrational Journey"
        - Draft [typed by Gerald Barrett], typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 329, Folder 3256)
        - Draft [with notes by GW], typescript, photocopy, corrected, n.d. (Box 329, Folder 3257)
        - Draft [final typescript, copy-edited by Peter Deane], typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 329, Folder 3258)
        - Excerpt: "Notes on Leningrad", printed version, Vogue, 1966 Oct 15 (Box 329, Folder 3259)
      - [Untitled outline for story], typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 329, Folder 3260)
    - Rothschild, Philippe, Baron de
      - "Auckland" [account of Pauline de Rothschild's illness], typescript, photocopy, 1970 (Box 329, Folder 3261)
    - Rouda, F. H.
      - "Below, Beneath, Under", typescript, photocopy (Box 329, Folder 3262)
    - Schuyler, George S.
      - "Farewell to Carlo", typescript, photocopy, 1964 Dec 23 (Box 329, Folder 3263)
    - Soyer, Raphael
      - "Tribute to [Jacques] Lipchitz", typescript, photocopy, n.d. (Box 329, Folder 3264)
    - Stevens, Wallace
      - "Cy est pourtraict..." and "Sunday Morning", French translations by Claude Heckscher, typescript, carbon (Box 329, Folder 3265)
    - Stevenson, John
      - "Paris and Synchronicities", computer printout (Box 329, Folder 3266)
    - Szold Fritz, Bernardine
      - "Remembrances", typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 329, Folder 3267-3268)
    - Tanner, Allen
      - "The Early Tchelitchew", typescript carbon, corrected, 1963 Nov 1 (Box 329, Folder 3269)
    - Wilder, Isabel
      - "The Grateful Badger", typescript, 1980 (Box 329, Folder 3270)
    - Windham, Donald
      - Tanaquil, revised paragraph, page 256, typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 329, Folder 3271)
    - Young, Ian
      - [Collection of poems], typescript, photocopy, n.d. (Box 329, Folder 3272)
    - [Unidentified]
      - "Orchestra Seat" fragment, typescript carbon, corrected, [1945] (Box 329, Folder 3273)
      - [Collection of poems and play scenes], holograph, typescript and carbon, 1980, n.d. (Box 329, Folder 3274)
- Personal Papers, 1918-87; Series IV; 14.28; (34 boxes)
  Series IV, Personal Papers, consists of
  eighteen subseries, all of which are arranged
  alphabetically.
  - ANNOUNCEMENTS AND PROGRAMS
    - Art exhibitions, 1939-74 (Box 330, Folder 3275-3279)
    - Events, 1950-82 (Box 330, Folder 3280)
    - Theater and Ballet, 1949-85, n.d. (Box 331, Folder 3281-3282)
    - Madrigal singers (University of Maryland) concert honoring Katherine Anne Porter, Barbara Wescott, GW and MW, 1969 Nov 14 (Box 331, Folder 3283)
  - ANTHOLOGIES AND COMMONPLACE BOOKS
    - "Anthology", 1951, n.d. (Box 331, Folder 3284)
    - "Aphorisms, etc.", 1969 (Box 331, Folder 3285)
    - "Aphorisms for Monroe", ca. 1940-56 (Box 331, Folder 3286)
    - Barbara Wescott's copybook, continued (Box 332, Folder 3287)
      - by GW, 1935, 1976
    - Birthday aphorism notebook for "John", 1960 (Box 332, Folder 3288)
    - Blue book for MW, 1942 (Box 332, Folder 3289)
    - Blue book for MW transcribed on notebook pages, n.d. (Box 332, Folder 3290-3291)
    - "A commonplace book for Pauline", 1948 Feb (Box 333, Folder 3292)
    - "A copybook for John Robert Connolly", 1971-78 (Box 333, Folder 3293)
    - "GW-1952" (Box 333, Folder 3294)
    - "GW-1952" [transcribed into notebook] (Box 333, Folder 3295)
    - "GW's selection of poems", n.d. (Box 333, Folder 3296-3297)
    - "The makings of a commonplace book", ca. 1950 (Box 334, Folder 3298)
    - Notebooks of aphorisms, ca. 1948-55 (Box 334, Folder 3299-3301)
    - Notebooks of aphorisms, ca. 1948-55 (Box 335, Folder 3302-3305)
    - "Pauline's anthology", n.d. (Box 335, Folder 3306)
    - "Phrases for Pauline", n.d. (Box 336, Folder 3307)
    - "Poems dear to me", ca. 1955-67 (Box 336, Folder 3308)
    - "Reading matter", ca. 1948-52 (Box 336, Folder 3309)
    - Zone [by Apollinaire] and other poems (Box 336, Folder 3310)
    - [Loose pages of aphorisms], n.d. (Box 336, Folder 3311)
  - AUTHOR'S LEAGUE/AUTHOR'S GUILD
    - Correspondence and memos, 1964-86 (Box 336, Folder 3312)
    - GW's notebook, 1960-63 (Box 337, Folder 3313-3314)
    - Documents re. copyright, 1963-65 (Box 337, Folder 3315)
    - Publications, 1949-74 (Box 337, Folder 3316)
    - Publications, 1949-74 (Box 337, Folder 3317)
  - CONTRACTS
    - Arbor House, The Grandmothers, 1984 (Box 337, Folder 3318)
    - TV-Radio Workshop, 1953 (Box 337, Folder 3319)
    - GW as speaker in "The Writer's World", 1966 Dec 6 (Box 337, Folder 3320)
  - INTERVIEW TRANSCRIPTS
    - "Alone", 1980 Mar 9 (Box 337, Folder 3321)
    - "At Jane Gunther's-first reading to guests", 1979 Jun 27 (Box 338, Folder 3322)
    - "Cocteau/GW at Bond St.", 1979 Feb 15 (Box 338, Folder 3323)
    - "Conversation re. Paul Robeson" [with Gledhill Cameron], 1976 Nov 26 (Box 338, Folder 3324)
    - "Conversation with WSM [Maugham] and GW", transcribed by MW, 1943 Feb 27 (Box 338, Folder 3325)
    - "Education-M. and J. Chute", 1979 Mar 13 (Box 338, Folder 3326)
    - "Eleanor Wolff", 1978 Nov 29 (Box 338, Folder 3327)
    - "England and Some Germany...with Jane Gunther", 1979 Mar 19 (Box 338, Folder 3328)
    - "Family Life Prior to 1914", 1979 Feb 4 (Box 338, Folder 3329)
    - "For Liz Smith-Christopher Street and Charlie Knickerbocker", 1979 Apr 27 (Box 338, Folder 3330)
    - "GW and Kinsey Institute", 1979 Dec 26 (Box 338, Folder 3331)
    - "GW and Sister Elizabeth James", 1979 Oct 26 (Box 338, Folder 3332)
    - "GW at Jane Gunther's", 1978 Jun 27 (Box 338, Folder 3333)
    - "GW on Max Jacob", n.d. (Box 338, Folder 3334)
    - "GW to JC", 1979 Nov (Box 338, Folder 3335-3336)
    - "Glenway Wescott on Tchelitchew", n.d. (Box 338, Folder 3337)
    - "Greenwich Village-1924", 1979 Mar 9 (Box 338, Folder 3338)
    - "The Harrison Family History", 1978 Nov 24 (Box 338, Folder 3339-3340)
    - "Indiana University Oral History Project", 1972 (Box 339, Folder 3341)
      [Includes: agreement and cover letter]
    - "Interview Given to Gilbert Harrison, the Wilder Biographer", 1980 May 17 (Box 339, Folder 3342)
    - "Paragraphs while cleaning house", n.d. (Box 339, Folder 3343)
    - "Prof. Terrence, Patterson, N.J. and Patricia Terry, June 28 all afternoon. Rambling Reminiscences" (Box 339, Folder 3344)
    - "U. of C. and Santa Fe 1918-20", 1979 Feb 5 (Box 339, Folder 3345)
    - "Unmarked tape-Mrs. Walter L. Weil", 1979 Feb 6 (Box 339, Folder 3346)
    - "Wescott Family Tree", 1976 Sep 22 (Box 339, Folder 3347)
    - "With Mrs. E.U. Johnson-Mrs. Fritz and Barbara Young", 1979 Jun 18 (Box 339, Folder 3348)
    - Untitled interview re. writing and early life (Box 339, Folder 3349)
    - Unidentified loose pages, n.d. (Box 339, Folder 3350)
  - LISTS
    - Animal group names, n.d. (Box 339, Folder 3351)
    - GW's list of authors, as to their sexual orientation, 1954 (Box 339, Folder 3352)
    - French plant names, n.d. (Box 339, Folder 3353)
    - Attendees of Mary Aldis's party, 1918 May 19 (Box 339, Folder 3354)
    - Names of people, n.d. (Box 339, Folder 3355)
    - Paris restaurants (from Colette Deman), n.d. (Box 339, Folder 3356)
    - Photographs, n.d. (Box 339, Folder 3357)
    - GW works collected by GPL, n.d. (Box 339, Folder 3358)
  - MAPS
    - Kewaskum, WI, [1955] (Box 339, Folder 3359)
    - Lambertville, NJ, n.d. (Box 339, Folder 3360)
    - London (Box 339, Folder 3361)
    - Mexico City and Guatemala, 1980, n.d. (Box 339, Folder 3362)
    - Rosemont, NJ [area], 1978, n.d. (Box 339, Folder 3363)
  - MENUS
    - Airplane menu, n.d. (Box 339, Folder 3364)
    - "Menus of 1943" (Box 339, Folder 3365)
    - Dinner for Walter Tracy and Herman Zapf at Grolier Club, 1955 Oct 19 (Box 340, Folder 3366)
    - Mouton, 1972-74 (Box 340, Folder 3367)
  - NOTEBOOKS
    - "Documents having to do with my journals", 1972 Aug 28 (Box 340, Folder 3368)
    - Hay Meadows garden, n.d. (Box 340, Folder 3369)
    - "New Stone-Blossom Housekeeping", [1948] (Box 340, Folder 3370)
    - Recipes, notes, n.d. (Box 340, Folder 3371)
    - Sayings by Anna Brakke, 1950s (Box 341, Folder 3372)
    - "Titles, Epiphanies, etc.", 1942 (Box 341, Folder 3373)
    - Untitled pocket notebooks, ca. 1973 (Box 341, Folder 3374)
  - NOTECARDS
    - Notes on Art, n.d. (Box 341, Folder 3375)
    - Bibliographic citations, n.d. (Box 341, Folder 3376)
    - Dinner menus, 1963 (Box 341, Folder 3377)
    - GW chronology, ca. 1920s-70s (Box 341, Folder 3378-3384)
    - GW chronology, n.d. (Box 342, Folder 3385-3392)
    - GW chronology, n.d. (Box 343, Folder 3393-3394)
    - Ideas for writings, ca. 1930s-50s (Box 343, Folder 3395)
    - Lists of names and titles (Box 343, Folder 3396)
    - Museum of Modern Art, n.d. (Box 343, Folder 3397)
    - Names of people with suggested fictional aliases, n.d. (Box 343, Folder 3398)
    - Plants, 1952-56 (Box 343, Folder 3399)
    - "Poor Glenway Wescott's Almanac", n.d. (Box 343, Folder 3400)
    - Queries (for GW chronology?), n.d. (Box 343, Folder 3401)
    - Quotations, n.d. (Box 343, Folder 3402)
    - "Rough list: pictures in sub-basement closet #050", n.d. (Box 343, Folder 3403)
    - [re: sex and pornographic films] (Box 343, Folder 3404)
    - [For speech at New York Public Library?], n.d. (Box 343, Folder 3405)
    - [Speech for Betsey Robbins?], n.d. (Box 343, Folder 3406)
    - [re. Tchelitchew works], ca. 1930s-50s (Box 343, Folder 3407)
    - "To Do" notes, n.d. (Box 344, Folder 3408)
    - [For writings?], n.d. (Box 344, Folder 3409)
    - [For writings?], n.d. (Box 344, Folder 3410-3411)
    - Miscellaneous subjects, n.d. (Box 344, Folder 3412)
  - NOTES
    - re: Chronology of events, n.d. (Box 344, Folder 3413)
      [by GW and GPL]
    - GW note to BW at the opening ceremonies of the Hunterdon Medical Center, 1953 Jun 28 (Box 344, Folder 3414)
    - "Notes on Contemporary Wisdom", n.d. (Box 344, Folder 3415)
    - "Homoerotic Films", n.d. (Box 344, Folder 3416)
    - "Italian notes preparatory to the honeymoon journey, midsummer 1935" (Box 344, Folder 3417)
    - re: GW journals, 1950s (Box 344, Folder 3418)
    - re: Katherine Anne Porter-GW letters, n.d. (Box 344, Folder 3419)
    - re: Pueblo dish and Santa Fe, 1976 Mar 7 (Box 344, Folder 3420)
    - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 344, Folder 3421-3423)
    - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 345, Folder 3424-3426)
    - Notes by others, n.d. (Box 345, Folder 3427)
  - PORTER, KATHERINE ANNE, MATERIAL
    - Memorial invitations, 1980 Oct 18 (Box 345, Folder 3428)
    - KAP letter to Saturday Review of Literature re: Ezra Pound, mimeograph copy, 1949 Jul 3 (Box 345, Folder 3429)
    - Franklin Library 100 Greatest Books of the Twentieth Century: notes and lists, 1977 (Box 345, Folder 3430)
    - Program, Brandeis University Creative Arts Award, 1972 (Box 345, Folder 3431)
  - PROJECTS
    - Ivan Ashby's visa: correspondence, forms and documentation, 1970 (Box 345, Folder 3432)
    - Joseph Blumenthal typography: examples, 1968-70 (Box 345, Folder 3433)
    - Bookbinding: clippings and sketches (Box 345, Folder 3434)
      [possible related to A Typographical Commonplace Book ]
    - UNESCO copyright proposal: draft, n.d. (Box 345, Folder 3435)
    - Karen Horney Clinic art sale: notebook with correspondence and notes, 1957-65 (Box 346, Folder 3436)
    - "The Last Months of My Mother's Life": notes written by Josephine Wescott, 1959-60 (Box 346, Folder 3437-3440)
    - Lynes, George Platt
      - GPL article and publicity, 1944-93 (Box 346, Folder 3441)
      - Appraisal of GPL collection, 1983, n.d. (Box 346, Folder 3442)
      - Correspondence re: GPL, 1956 (Box 346, Folder 3443)
      - GPL exhibition and consigments documents, 1979-80, n.d. (Box 346, Folder 3444)
      - GPL exhibition catalogs, 1932-60 (Box 346, Folder 3445)
      - Lists of photographs and notes re: GPL, 1952-80 (Box 347, Folder 3446-3447)
      - GPL Model release forms, 1952-55 (Box 347, Folder 3448)
      - Photocopies of GPL photographs, 1979-80 (Box 347, Folder 3449)
      - Photograph reproduction receipts, n.d. (Box 347, Folder 3450)
      - Empty photograph sleeves, 1934-53 (Box 347, Folder 3451)
    - Parke-Bernet: notes and lists (Box 347, Folder 3452)
    - Eugene F. Saxton Memorial Trust: guidelines, n.d. (Box 347, Folder 3453)
  - SCRAPBOOKS
    - "American Beauty", n.d. (Box 347, Folder 3454)
    - "Bizarreries", n.d. (Box 347, Folder 3455)
    - "E" (nude males), n.d. (Box 348, Folder 3456)
    - GW's "eye" book, n.d. (Box 348, Folder 3457)
    - "Scrapbook III", n.d. (Box 348, Folder 3458)
  - SITWELL, EDITH, MATERIAL
    - Announcement of performance of Facade at the Museum of Modern Art, 1949 Jan 19 (Box 349, Folder 3459)